

QA ENGINEER

052-3415404mkeren4@gmail.comBeer Yakov

QA LINGINEL

PROFILE

With 9 years of experience as an Instructional Designer and Video Editor, I am an expert at creating engaging and effective learning experiences for e-learning courses, training videos, marketing videos, user guides, and other learning materials. Now, I'm eager to make a career change to QA and I recently successfully completed a QA Expert Course from Analiza, and I gained high skills and knowledge during a three-month temporary role as Manual QA Engineer.

EDUCATION

- 2024 Automation Course Online Gal Matalon
- 2023 QA Expert Course, "Analiza".
- 2023 Product Management Course in gaming, "Hands on games".
- 2019 Product Manager Course, Technion The school of continuing education.
- 2014 Bachelor's degree with honors in "Learning Systems Technologies". "HIT Holon Institute of Technology".
- 2007- Bachelor's degree in Film and Television Arts academic excellence. "Sapir Academic College".

EXPERIENCE

- 2023-2024 During my three-month temporary role as a Manual QA Engineer in a startup company, I focused
 on creating test cases, identifying bugs, analyze logs information to reproduce bugs accurately, executing tests,
 and performing releases under pressure, which includes matinance, sanity and regression test. I collaborated
 closely with team members, including developers and product managers, to enhance the software's quality.
- 2019-2022 Instructional designer and Video editor for companies Comeet and Nano Dimension.
 In this role, I conducted effective interviews with SMEs, determined learning needs, and structured engaging learning content and developed materials, including scripts, storyboards, and UI, as well as custom graphics.
 The role required creativity, strong technical skills, excellent communication and a strong customer focus.
- My main achievements included creating a set of design principles for developing training videos
 and templates that have improved training quality and effectiveness by 90% as well as creating instructional
 videos that have reduced repetitive questions from customers by 50%.
- 2017-2019 Instructional designer and Video editor in HP Indigo.
 - This role entailed taking ownership of a learning project: planning, executing, and analyzing lerner feedback, as well as making any necessary revisions to the learning materials. Additionally, I have worked with crossfunctional teams, including product, customer success, marketing, and operations.
- My main achievements included establishing design principles for the production of training videos, templates, and other learning materials that increase learning experiences and engagement by 90% as well as Developing an online learning program that produced a 95% completion rate.
- 2016-2017 Instructional designer and Video editor in Mellanox.

As part of this role, I was responsible for producing polished and professional-looking videos, as well as ensuring that the learning products met the desired learning outcomes.

The role required the ability to bridge the technological gap between technical and non-technical staff and to manage multiple learning projects simultaneously in a dynamic environment.

SKILLS

- Strong Technical and Management skills
- Strong problem solving and High Customer Orientation
- Basic Knowledge with System log analysis Coralogix and Logrocket
- QA methodologies and Test documentation (STP, STD)
- Python, Selenium WebDriver, pyTest, POM
- SQL (Join Level), HTML5, CSS3
- Jira, X-RAY, Slack and Monday softwares
- Familiarity with REST API, Postman, Allure, Github and Jenkins
- Micoroft Office (Word, Excel Functions, Pivot table and Vlookup)
- High understanding of UX/UI principles
- Adobe video Editing and Adobe Graphic Design Photoshop, InDesign CS5, Illustrator

MILITARY SERVICE

- Instructor training combat soldiers in the signal corps.
- Commander office responsible for organizing the course, as well managing the feedback for new instructors.

LANGUAGES

- English Professional (both written and verbal).
- Hebrew Native.

